I've been asked many times what my
number one interview was tough question
but for over 50's life cover the
nation's number one choice is clear the
guaranteed over 50 plan from
sunlife we don't like to leave something
for our loved ones to help with funeral
cost or as a cash gift and with the
nation's number one you can do just that
if you're age between 50 and 85 you're
guaranteed to be accepted without any
health questions cover starts from just
£4 a month you can't get this kind of
cover for less after you've had the plan
for two years a cash sum is paid when
you're
gone call this number today the first
month's premium is free you get a free
pen just for inquiring and a welcome
gift when you
join why not put your family first with
the number one choice call free on 850
5550 or visit
okay